[{"answer": "I..", "docId": "Verdict_-The.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "...I was a friend of your fa..", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "I'm... Mrs. my friend? I'm my friend... why didn't you go in", "docId": "Verdict_-The.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": " It's locked", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "...we, we love her, my friend and me..", "docId": "Verdict_-The.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "But what can we do? She don't know who's visiting her..", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "I read the hospital report on your client", "docId": "Verdict_-The.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "...my friend..", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "They called, they're going to settle, what I want to do is build up as much..", "docId": "Verdict_-The.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "The Archdiocese called, they want to settle... her estate..", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Her doctors murdered her. They gave her the wrong anesthetic and they put her in the hospital for life.  Her doctors murdered her", "docId": "Verdict_-The.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "I read the file. Yeah. my friend and my friend. I know who they were", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "...that's perfectly all right", "docId": "Verdict_-The.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": " To do right. Isn't that why you're doing it", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "How did you settle on the amount", "docId": "Verdict_-The.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "You thought it was just", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Because it struck me how neatly 'three' went into the amount. Two Hundred Ten Thousand. That would mean I keep seventy", "docId": "Verdict_-The.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Yes. It would be", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "that place versus Electric Boat", "docId": "Verdict_-The.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "I had a good teacher. my friend versus Urban Transport..", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "my friend? Bushmills.  Lookit, do me a favor. I'll buy you a drink tomorrow", "docId": "Verdict_-The.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "I'm going to get laid", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Still looking", "docId": "Verdict_-The.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "I changed my room at the Hotel", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "The TV didn't work", "docId": "Verdict_-The.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "And what are you? A cop", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "And what are you? A cop", "docId": "Verdict_-The.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "My e", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Yes. It was, actually", "docId": "Verdict_-The.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Who says I'm the one that called it off", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "my friend", "docId": "Verdict_-The.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "What if it wasn't you that I came back to see", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": " Maybe I can do something right", "docId": "Verdict_-The.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "That's what I'm going to try to do", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "my friend can't make it. He had an appointment he forgot, he's going to see you later. I'm my friend, we're supposed to get to know each other", "docId": "Verdict_-The.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "So far you're great. You got a cigarette", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Why don't you get some rest", "docId": "Verdict_-The.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "You can't work if you can't think. You get in bed. It's all right. I'll stay here with you. It's all right. Come on..", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": " What is your name, please", "docId": "Verdict_-The.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": " You were my friend's doctor...", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "Say it", "docId": "Verdict_-The.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "You were the anesthesiologist at her delivery May twelfth, nineteen seventy..", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "D'you find the obstetric nurse", "docId": "Verdict_-The.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Gimme the address. I'm gonna go. We're going to need her", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "I've got nothing to say to you", "docId": "Verdict_-The.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "Nothing happened", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "Who says that I'm protecting anyone", "docId": "Verdict_-The.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "I don't owe them a goddamn thing", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "I do. Who is it? The Doctors. What do you owe them", "docId": "Verdict_-The.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "Then why don't you testify", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "Why is that", "docId": "Verdict_-The.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "...that's what the sister said. The chart said she ate nine hours prior to..", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "Well, then what are you doing here", "docId": "Verdict_-The.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "You do what you want. You want to leave... You want to go kill yourself", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "Is there going to be a later...", "docId": "Verdict_-The.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "If I don't 'grow up...", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "Nothing", "docId": "Verdict_-The.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "Very good", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": "Dr. my friend, just so the Jury knows, you never treated my friend. Is that correct", "docId": "Verdict_-The.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": "Engaged to render an opinion. For a price. Is that correct? You're being paid to be here today", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": "Engaged to render an opinion. For a price. Is that correct? You're being paid to be here today", "docId": "Verdict_-The.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": "Are you boar", "qsentId": 62}, {"answer": "Are you boar", "docId": "Verdict_-The.txt", "asentId": 65, "question": "...I'm sure it is, but this is that place, Doctor. Certified in Internal Medicine", "qsentId": 64}, {"answer": "I'm just an M.D", "docId": "Verdict_-The.txt", "asentId": 67, "question": "I know of him", "qsentId": 66}, {"answer": "How is that", "docId": "Verdict_-The.txt", "asentId": 69, "question": "What book is that", "qsentId": 68}, {"answer": "'Methodology and Techniques of Anesthesiology.' Yes", "docId": "Verdict_-The.txt", "asentId": 71, "question": "I am sevent", "qsentId": 70}, {"answer": "Thank you", "docId": "Verdict_-The.txt", "asentId": 73, "question": " Call the A.M.A.  ...I can't talk now.  ...tell them you're Dr. Somebody... you have to find this nurse..", "qsentId": 72}, {"answer": "my friend", "docId": "Verdict_-The.txt", "asentId": 75, "question": " My subscription lapsed three years ago..", "qsentId": 74}, {"answer": "You are aware of the penalties for perjury...", "docId": "Verdict_-The.txt", "asentId": 77, "question": "Yes.  It is a crime. A serious crime", "qsentId": 76}, {"answer": "...what in the world would induce you to make a photocopy of some obscure record and hold it four years? This is a... why? Why would you do that", "docId": "Verdict_-The.txt", "asentId": 79, "question": "And why, please tell us, would you think that", "qsentId": 78}]